(Sheldon:)That never gets old.
(Sheldon:)Release the Kraken!
(Sheldon:)Oh, chills.
(Sheldon:)Besides, I'm having dinner with Amy.
(Raj:)Oh, okay. I'll just go home and be alone.
(Raj:)Which is cool.
I eat alone, I sleep alone, I cry alone, so...
(Raj:)...cool.
(Sheldon:)Darn.
(Sheldon:)If you weren't busy I'd ask you to join us.
(Raj:)Really? I can come? Thanks.
Sheldon, are you sure you wanna bring Raj
on your date night?
(Sheldon:)Oh, absolutely.
(Sheldon:)I have a contractual obligation...
(Sheldon:)...to provide Amy with conversation
and casual physical contact.
(Sheldon:)But nowhere is it specified
that I can't outsource that to an Indian.
(Bernadette(on webcam):)Howie?
(Bernadette(on webcam):)- Howie?
- Hey, there's my beautiful bride.
(Howard:)- Can you see me?
- I can.